DataBase = [
    {
        "question": "What does Bangladesh's flag look like?",
        "choices": ["Blue background with yellow star in centre", "Green background with red circle in centre", "Green background with white star in centre", "Red background with white circle in centre"],
        "answer": "Green background with red circle in centre"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did Bangladesh finally become independent and gain the name it has today?",
        "choices": ["1947", "1952", "1970", "1971"],
        "answer": "1971"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the national flower of Bangladesh?",
        "choices": ["Rose", "Tulip", "Water lily", "Daffodil"],
        "answer": "Water lily"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did Bangladesh become known as after its first session of Independence in 1947?",
        "choices": ["East Pakistan", "West Pakistan", "Easr India", "West India"],
        "answer": "East Pakistan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main religion practiced in Bangladesh?",
        "choices": ["Islam", "Christianity", "Buddism", "Hinduism"],
        "answer": "Islam"
    },
    {
        "question": "On which continent is Bangladesh located?",
        "choices": ["Africa", "Asia", "Europe", "North America"],
        "answer": "Asia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which district of Bangladesh was part of Assam?",
        "choices": ["Chittagong", "Khulna", "Chapai Nawabganj", "Sylhet"],
        "answer": "Sylhet"
    },
    {
        "question": "To which Indian Lieutenant General did Pakistani Lieutenant General Niazi surrendered?",
        "choices": ["P Gopalakrishna Menon", "Rajinder Dewan", "Jagjit Singh Aurora", "Tarun Kumar Aich"],
        "answer": "Jagjit Singh Aurora"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which river of Bangladesh originates in Tibet?",
        "choices": ["Brahmaputra", "Padma", "Surma", "Jamuna"],
        "answer": "Brahmaputra"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which area of sea lies to the south of Bangladesh?",
        "choices": ["South China Sea", "Andaman Sea", "Bay of Bengal", "Laccadive Sea"],
        "answer": "Bay of Bengal"
    }
]